Hidey ho, all you
"South Park"-a-teers out there.
Hidey ho!
I'm rootin' tootin'
Trey Parker.
And I'm pistol-slingin'
Matt Stone.
And this here's
old Scratch.
Say hi, old fella.
Hi, Scratch.
You know, Matt and I are
right excited
about this next episode
of "South Park,"
because it's our
favorite episode.
That's right.
It's called "Starvin' Marvin,"
and it originally aired
on Thanksgiving.
In it, the boys celebrate
the holiday
with a visitor
from a far-off land.
You know, when Comedy Central
Called us and asked us
to do a Thanksgiving special,
the first thing that
went through my mind was,
"Boy, I'd like to have
sex with Jennifer Aniston."
Cup her perky breasts
in my hands
and put my hand
back and kind of--
nice little
tight buns there.
But you know,
the thing about this episode
is that it teaches
racial tolerance,
to treat everyone
as an equal regardless
of the color
of their skin.
Oh, look,
it's our Indian friend,
Indian Companion.
Say hi, kids.
Hi!
What's happenin',
Indian Companion?
Something coming.
Grizzly bear.
Oh, well, why don't you
go over there
and kick him
in the balls?
Grizzly bears like
being kicked in the balls.
Dumb ass.
- He's so stupid.
Well, why don't you all
sit back and have
a rootin' tootin' good time
with "Starvin' Marvin"?
Yee-ha!
Hooray!
♪ I'm going down
to South Park ♪
♪ Gonna have
myself a time ♪
♪ Friendly faces
everywhere ♪
♪ Humble folks
without temptation ♪
♪ Going down
to South Park ♪
♪ Gonna leave my
woes behind ♪
♪ Ample parking
day or night ♪
♪ People spouting:
"Howdy neighbor." ♪
♪ Headed on up
to South Park ♪
♪ Gonna see if
I can't unwind ♪
♪ So come on down
to South Park ♪
♪ And meet some
friends of mine ♪
That was awesome!
- Yeah!
Would you boys
like some Cheesy Poofs?
Get out of the way, mom!
The "Terrance and Phillip"
Thanksgiving Special is on.
Sure, hon.
And yeah,
we want Cheesy Poofs!
Hey, Terrance, looks like
this might
be a good
place to start a new colony.
It sure does, Phillip.
No one will oppress
our religion here.
You stained
my pilgrim hat, butt-pipe!
Did you guys see that?
That was sweet.
Coming up next
on the "Terrance and Phillip"
Thanksgiving Special, Phillip
farts on Terrance and laughs.
Oh, cool.
And now a word
from our sponsor.
Here in the heart
of Africa, children are dying.
Not from disease or war,
but from hunger.
I'm Sally Struthers.
These children are in desperate
need, and only you can help.
Hey, who's that fat chick?
Sally Struthers, dude.
She used to be on "Full House."
Oh.
You see, here,
in the middle of Africa,
food is extremely scarce.
Doesn't look like she's
having
any trouble finding food.
Yeah,
she's fatter than Cartman.
Yeah.
Hey!
For just $5 a month,
you can sponsor a child.
That's stupid, who
the hell would want to do that?
Sponsor now,
and we'll also
send you this Teiko digital
sports watch as a free gift.
Kick ass!
Sweet!
- Whoo-hoo!
I'll call--I know
my mom's credit card number.
Did they say
if it's waterproof?
Hello?
Is this Sally Struthers?
Oh.
- What did she say?
Shut up butt-pirate,
I'm trying to hear.
Ass-rammer.
- Yeah? Yeah.
We want to adopt
a starving Ether-nopian.
When do we
get the sports watch?
Just a second fat-ass!
- You vas-deferens!
Hello?
No, no, it's a ma--
Vas-deferens?
Oh.
Ask her if we get
the watch right away.
Do we get the sports
watch right away?
- She says we do.
- Cool.
I get to wear it first,
you guys.
I can't wait to get out
of school
and get
our Teiko sports watch.
Yeah, but I get
to wear it first, I said.
Children, children!
To honor this special time
of year, we'll be
doing a canned food drive.
Does anybody know
what a canned food drive is?
Yes, Eric?
When they cut up a chick's
stomach
to get a baby out?
No, that's a Caesarian
Section, Eric, but that's okay,
remember, there are no stupid
questions, just stupid people.
A canned food drive is
when we collect canned food
for poor people who can't
afford to eat on Thanksgiving.
You mean, like Kenny?
- Exactly.
Mr. Garrison?
Why do poor people
always smell like sour milk?
I don't know, Eric,
they just do.
Now, children,
I want each of you to bring
in one can of food.
And later,
the mayor of South Park will
divide it up amongst Kenny's
family and other poor people.
I'm not bringing in food
for poor people, screw them!
Don't you want to help
those who are less fortunate?
Hey you guys,
do you hear something?
I--I think I hear
the flower children calling!
This is the one time of year
you're supposed to care
about people who can't eat!
Isn't it
enough that I pay taxes?
What about the poor
houses that I pay for?
Many would rather
die than go to those places!
Well then,
perhaps they should,
and decrease
the surplus population!
Okay, kids, that's
enough Dickens for one day.
Let's get on with our lesson,
right, Mr. Hat?
That's right,
Mr. Garrison,
Englebert Humperdink
was the first person
on the moon.
Who was the second?
Aaaah!
What the hell is going on?
- Aaaah!
Well,
you don't see that every day.
Okay, now, once we have all
the canned foods collected,
we'll need some clever way
to distribute them to the poor.
It should be
something festive.
Mayor,
we've got a very big problem.
Ah, you're that insane
genetic engineer
from up on the hill, right?
Yes, and I may have
made a horrible mistake.
I was trying
to genetically engineer
turkeys
for Thanksgiving.
Uh-huh.
You know,
to provide food for the needy.
Of course.
Well, something went wrong
and the turkeys broke free.
And the worst part is,
they're really pissed off.
Naturally.
Oh, do go on.
We have to stop them or--or
they could destroy everything.
Time is short.
You were saying?
They act just like normal
turkeys, except they're evil.
Oh, my!
Somehow I don't think
you're taking me seriously.
Now why
would you say that?
Did it come?
Did it come? Is it here yet?
I get to use
it first, you guys!
Mom, did our digital
sports watch come yet?
Not yet, hon.
Damn.
- Hey, look, you guys.
And now, back to Part 2
of the "Terrance and Phillip"
Thanksgiving Special.
I sure am cold, Phillip.
Yes, and hungry too.
Being a pilgrim
totally sucks ass.
Gosh, I hope we
don't starve.
Ah, a squeaker!
The digital
sports watch is here!
What the hell?
Dude, that's not
a digital sports watch.
Hey, it looks like
one of those Ether-opians.
Oh, man, they must
have accidentally sent him
instead of the sports watch.
Maybe they took it literally
when we said
we wanted to adopt a kid.
Whoa! That was cool.
Yeah, how did he
make those clicking sounds?
What's your name dude?
- Mabin.
I think he said
his name is Marvin.
Yeah, Starvin' Marvin.
Nice to meet
you, Starvin' Marvin.
Hey, mom?
- Yes, hon?
We found a Ether-opian,
can we keep him?
Sure, hon.
- Sweet.
Dude, let's bring
him to school tomorrow.
Come on,
Starvin' Marvin,
I want you to meet
my little brother.
No, no! He's my son!
I adopted him.
It was my mom's credit card.
Okay, okay,
we'll switch off.
Starvin' Marvin can
stay here for a week,
then at Stan's, then with me.
Yeah, and never with Kenny,
because his family is too poor.
Totally.
- Ahh!
Look how the leaves
fall so delicately
on the surface
of the pond.
It's so beautiful.
Not as beautiful as you.
Oh, darling, look.
Thanksgiving turkeys.
Oh, they're so beautiful.
- Not as beautiful as you.
Look at the way
they foam at the mouth,
like beautiful suds of beer.
- Not as beautiful as-
This is a great way for you
to experience America,
Starvin' Marvin.
This is what we call
an 'all you can eat buffet.
Yeah, here you get to eat
all you want for only $6.99.
That's why we all come
here on Tuesday nights,
except for Kenny's
family, 'cause to them,
$6.99 is two years' income.
Why is your family
poor, Starvin' Marvin?
Is your dad an alcoholic too?
You see, Starvin' Marvin,
these are what
we call appetizers.
Ap-ee-tizer.
This is what
you eat before you eat,
to make you more hungry.
Well, food is here,
that's it for the appetizers.
No, Starvin' Marvin,
that's my pot-pie.
Cartman, you butt-pipe,
this is the time of year you're
supposed to share.
- Oh yeah, you're right.
Are you gonna eat
all of your peach cobbler?
No, you don't want all that.
Why don't you share it with me?
Just shove it
on over here.
Let me just have
some of that, huh?
Children, children!
I'm a little disappointed
in your Thanksgiving spirit.
Only a few cans have been
donated to our
canned food drive.
And can't we do
a little better than
creamed corn...
and...creamed corn?
Please bring in more diverse
food, children, or else
Kenny's family is going to have
a pretty corny Thanksgiving.
Corny. Gravy.
Corny
Thanksgiving, hoo!
Anyway, children,
I understand a few of you have
brought in something
special for show-and-tell.
Yeah, yeah, we do!
All right, boys,
show us what you've brought.
This is our new Ether-nopian,
Starvin' Marvin.
He can do really
cool stuff with his voice.
Show 'em, Starvin' Marvin.
No, Starvin' Marvin,
that's Kenny's creamed corn.
that's a bad Starvin' Marvin!
Boys,
what the hell are you doing?
This is horribly,
horribly wrong.
How did you get this child?
He was accidentally
delivered to us
instead
of a sports watch.
The sports watch
from the commercial?
Yeah, that one.
- I want a Starvin' Marvin.
Me too.
- Yes, I'll pay $50 for one.
Boys, you're too
young to take care of a child.
I'm afraid I'm going
to have to call
the Red
Cross and have him returned.
Ah,
I told you we shouldn't have
brought him to school dude.
Okay, thank you very much.
Yes, you can pick
him up tonight. Bye now.
Now, boys, I hope
you've learned your lesson.
No.
You can't
care for this child!
But I thought we were
supposed
to care
on Thanksgiving.
Yes,
but you don't actually get
involved with
the child's lives.
You're supposed
to just send money,
and once in a while
they write you a letter.
You see, Marvin didn't grow up
in a normal
place like South Park.
So why can't
he live here now?
Because he can't!
- Because why?
Because eight year
olds can't be parents!
Then you take care of him.
I can't.
I--Umm, I'm very busy.
I send my $5 a month, see?
This sucks,
Starvin' Marvin is our friend.
Oh well, back
to the poor country with you.
You better watch
what you say, Cartman!
You might be poor
and hungry some day.
Yeah, right.
I knew that you
were the only person
who would
listen to me, Chef.
Yeah, well,
let's get it over with.
This place gives
me the Bubujeebies.
Look here in my microscope.
Tell me what you see.
Uhh, I see
an extreme close-up
of Vanessa Redgrave's
private parts.
Oh, whoops.
Now tell me what you see.
Well, I'm no biologist,
but I'd say it
looks like turkey DNA.
Precisely, but look
how rapidly it's dividing.
What does it mean?
Means the turkeys are
growing at an exponential rate.
If we don't destroy them all,
they'll take over the town.
Maybe the world.
- Oh, fudge!
Uhh, let me see that
Vanessa Redgrave thing again.
Sure.
Hello there, little boy,
we're looking for a starving
African child who was
accidentally sent here instead
of a Teiko sports watch.
Hey, hey,
what's going on?
Hey, let go of me!
Hey!
Hey! I'll kick you in the nuts.
Okay, man?
Here's your sports watch,
son, sorry for the mix-up.
Hey! Hey, seriously!
Hey, you're pissing me off!
Sweet.
So how does this thing work?
Well mayor,
it's based on the cash grab,
but instead of money,
the cans of food
are blown around
inside the capsule.
The pov inside catches as many
as he can to feed his family.
Pov?
- Poverty stricken citizen.
Oh-ho-ho, brilliant.
What the hell is this?
I don't know, mayor,
I don't think it's
listed on the program.
They're increasing
in number, mayor.
These are the vicious
turkeys I warned you about.
It's true mayor!
Those turkeys just
ripped apart my cafeteria!
Whoa!
You won't get away with this,
you bastards!
Wow! Those are
some pissed off turkeys!
Okay, people, don't panic!
Bring out the defense squad!
We need more than that!
They'll only come
back in increased numbers!
Hey, Phillip,
could you pass the beans?
Beans? Uh oh,
looks like we'll be
at war with these
Indians soon.
Wait, wait, wait.
Here it comes.
Aaaaah,
I crapped in my pants!
Aaaah!
I think you got some
spatter on Chief Running Wolf.
I spattered his face!
Now he's a smelly Indian!
We'll be back to part 14
of the "Terrance and Phillip"
Thanksgiving Special,
right after this.
Hunger is an enemy
that we all must fight.
These children
desperately need your support.
Hey,
somebody get me out of here!
This sucks!
So please,
call and adopt a child today.
I'm seriously
getting pissed off over here!!
You want some
more Cheesy Poofs, hon?
Ya, I won da Cheesy Poof.
Okay.
- Sweet.
This is serious
bull!
There has to be a Happy
Burger around here somewhere.
Excuse me, I am a lost
little boy--Could you help me?
Well, screw you too!
What the--Who the hell
let all these flies in here?
Hasn't anybody ever
heard of insect repellent?
All right, everyone,
it's time to give out
canned food to the poor.
Hey, where's Cartman?
I don't know. Do you
know where he is, Marvin?
Looks like we have the turkey
problem under control.
It's time to embrace
the spirit of giving
with the canned food grab.
Come on, hurry up.
Grab a lot son.
Happy happy Thanksgiving!
Let 'er rip!
Come on,
grab those cans, little boy!
- Come on, Kenny!
- Come on, son!
Now, let's see all
the goodies you're going
to take home to your family.
It looks like he got a--
a can of string beans!
What the--
Dude,
the mutant turkeys are back!
Okay people, move along,
nothing to see here,
you looky-loos.
I tried to tell you,
but you didn't listen.
Gather around everybody,
and listen good.
Go to your
homes and arm your--
What the hell are
you supposed to be anyway?
That's not
important right now.
No! What the hell is this
little thing supposed to be?
It doesn't look like anything.
Chef, the turkeys!
- Oh, All right.
Listen up everybody,
and listen good.
Go to your homes
and arm yourselves
with whatever you can.
We'll meet back here
in 15 minutes. Hurry!
We are not going
to let our Thanksgiving
be ruined
by a bunch of turkeys.
You guys, seriously,
I'm hungry.
I have to eat.
Ah, sweet!
The Red Cross!
I'll have fried chicken and a
side of mashed potatoes please.
Sorry, kid,
but we're out of food.
We ran out of funding.
What?
- We just didn't get
enough sponsors back home,
so now we've got
to pack it up.
But I'm not
a starving Ethiopian!
I have to get back home too!
Sorry dude,
we just don't have any funds.
Here, have
a Teiko sports watch.
Weak!
People, we all have to do our
part against the evil turkeys.
There's too many of them.
Come on! Where is
that Thanksgiving spirit?
We can't stop them.
Today,
you fight for your city!
You fight for your honor!
These turkeys will
continue to push until they
have taken everything from us!
These fudged-up turkeys
from the the crustaceous era
can take our lives,
but they can never
take our freedom!
Whoo! Yeah!
Whoo!
Here you go, turkeys!
Does my hair look okay?
Can't go on...
need...
appetizer...
I'm sorry, God!
I'm sorry I mocked poor people.
I'm sorry I
wasn't more sensitive.
Please, please, God.
My god has forsaken me.
Huh, I wonder what's in here?
Snacky Cakes!
Mmmm!
Sally Struthers?
- Who the hell are you?
Give me that cake!
- No, this is my cake!
No, Sally Struthers,
you give me that cake!
No! You can't have any!
No, Sally Struthers,
that's my cake!
You guys, Sally Struthers
is holding food from us!
Uh-oh.
Ahhh!
Stay close, children.
Oh, my God,
they've killed Kenny!
You bastards!
The last three are
getting away, shoot 'em, Ned!
We did it!
- My God, what have we done?
We've saved Thanksgiving.
But all those poor turkeys,
they're--they're all dead.
Every turkey dies,
not every turkey truly lives.
As horrible as they were,
they--they felt
like a part of me.
Perhaps I shouldn't be
toying with God's creations,
perhaps I should just--
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Excuse me sir,
we're looking for a little
starving Ethiopian boy
who was accidentally delivered
to South Park instead
of a Teiko sports watch.
Have you seen anyone
fitting this description.
Oh, that could be a hundred
kids in this town, mister.
There you are.
Are you ready to go home now?
Wow,
it sucks he has to leave.
Yeah, I like him
a lot more than Cartman.
You know, I think
I've learned something today.
It's really easy not to think
of images on TV as real people.
But they are.
That's why it's easy
to ignore those commercials,
but, people on TV are
just as real as you or I.
Yeah.
And that means that
MacGyver is a real person too.
We're terribly sorry
about the mix-up, little boy.
We'll get you
back home immediately.
That's right you will,
God damn it.
Move it povs,
I'm an American!
Lord, on this day of thanks,
we would like to extend
our deepest gratitude for this
incredible bounty
of green beans
you have
bestowed upon us.
And though for some
reason you found it necessary
to take our son from us,
and though you for some reason
find pleasure in watching us
suffer, still, we give thanks.
Amen.
- Amen.
Does anybody
have a can opener?
God Damn-it.